Guide to the Donald W. Baker College Veterinary Medicine Photograph Collection, 1950- 1969.
Baker, Donald W. College Veterinary Medicine Photograph Collection
- Unidentified man at a conference table, 1962 (Box 5c, Folder VPC.00481)
  Description: Unidentified man at a conference table, There's another man in foreground with back to the camera.
- George Goode, 1962 (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00482)
  Description: Candid of George Goode, class of 1945, paneled wall behind him. He is sitting at a table facing left with a cigarette in his hand. Robert Clark is visible in the background
- Lillian Paine, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00483)
  Description: Candid of Lillian Paine, library assistant, cataloging in the stacks.
- Alfred Graham, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00484)
  Description: Candid of Alfred Graham, College Engineer from ca. 1957-1968. He is sitting with a flash light in his hands.
- Alfred Graham, ca. 1960s (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00485)
  Description: Alfred Graham, College Engineer, sitting with a cup of coffee
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 7.5" 2 8" x 10", 2 prints on paper 1 print on cardboard
- Alfred Graham and Mr. Summer, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00486)
  Description: Alfred Graham, College Engineer, and Mr. Sumner decorating a Christmas tree in the lobby of Schurman Hall.
- Alfred Graham gesturing to a Christmas wreath, 1962 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00487)
  Description: Alfred Graham gesturing to a Christmas wreath
- Drs. Van Deusen, Palmer, and Haenel, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00488)
  Description: Candid of (left to right) Carlisle W. Van Deusen, class of 1944; L.G. Palmer; and William F. Haenel, class of 1950 at a Northern New York Veterinary Medical Association meeting. They are sitting at a conference table in front of a window. Van Deusen is
- Drs. Tucker, Van Deusen and Davis, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00489)
  Description: Candid of E. W. "Brud" Tucker (Class of 1941), C.W. Van Deusen (Class of 1944), and Arthur E. Davis (Class of 1944). They are standing in a parking lot. Van Deusen is wearing a hat and a bow tie. They are wearing conference badges.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 9.5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Drs. Edward Steinfeld and Kenneth F. Hilbert, ca. 1960s (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00490)
  Description: Candid of Edward F. Steinfeldt, class of 1941 and Kenneth F. Hilbert, class of 1928, and unidentified man sitting at a banquet table. There is a life preserver hanging on the wall behind them
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 2 prints on paper (cropped)
- Drs. Edward Steinfeld and Kenneth F. Hilbert, ca. 1960s (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00491)
  Description: Candid of Edward F. Steinfeldt, class of 1941, and Kenneth F. Hilbert, class of 1928, at a banquet table. One is standing, one is seated. There is a life preserver hanging on the wall behind them. It reads "1870 Show Boat."
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6.5" x 10", 1 print on paper
- Dr. Julius Fabricant, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00492)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Julius Fabricant standing in the back of a truck with two unidentified men and chickens
- Dr. Julius Fabricant, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00493)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Julius Fabricant standing in the back of a truck with an unidentified man and chickens
- Students with experimental cows, 1964 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00494)
  Description: Bruce L. Hull and Kenneth C. Hayes, both class of 1965, weighing a Holstein cow. Caption on back reads, "Experimental Calves in Parasitology." See also VPC.00495.
- Students with experimental cows, 1964 (Box 5c, Folder VPC.00495)
  Description: Students including an unidentified black student (graduate student?) weighing a Holstein cow. See also VPC.00494.
- Unidentified student with puppies, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00496)
  Description: Unidentified black student with puppies. Misidentified in Ellis Leonard list. See also VPC.00513
- Students outside, 1962 (Box 5c, Folder VPC.00497)
  Description: 8 male students gathered around a platform of some kind outside.
- Groups of students with a calf, 1964 (Box 5c, Folder VPC.00498)
  Description: Groups of students with a calf outside.
- John Ash, Miles Markham, Charles Morris, D. W. Baker, ca. 1940s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00499)
  Description: Group photo including John Ash, Miles Charles Morris, Donald W. Baker and six unidentified men. The group is outside. Most are wearing overcoats. Baker is in rain gear.
- Charles Rife and D. W. Baker, 1949 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00500)
  Description: Charles Rife, class of 1925 and D. W. Baker, class of 1929 with a cat in front of an exhibit
  Photographer (if other than Baker): John F. Brock, Cornell Photo Science Service
- D.W. Baker and Unidentified people in Peru, ca. 1940s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00501)
  Description: Candid of D.W. Baker, 2 unidentified men and 2 unidentified women in Peru. There's a neon sign in the window behind Baker that reads, "Restaura-." See also VPC.00502, VPC.00416 and VPC.00417.
  Photographer (if other than Baker): Photo Barraza
- D.W. Baker and Unidentified people in Peru, ca. 1940s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00502)
  Description: Candid of D.W. Baker, 2 unidentified men in Peru. There's a neon sign in the window behind Baker that reads, "Restaurant." See also VPC.00416, VPC.00417 and VPC.00501.
- Southern Tier Veterinary Medical Association Meeting, 1950 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00503)
  Description: Southern Tier Veterinary Medical Association meeting dinner in Corning, NY. Scene shows approximately sixty people in a room sitting at tables. Donald W. Baker is visible at the table furthest right and furthest back.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 6.5", 1 print on particle board
- James Sweet, D. W. Baker and unidentified man, ca. 1949 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00504)
  Description: Candid of James D. Sweet, class of 1932, D. W. Baker, and unidentified man. Two have their hands crossed. The third has his arms crossed.
- D. W. Baker, ca. 1940s (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00505)
  Description: D. W. Baker looking through a microscope on top of an overturned garbage can outside.
- Southern Tier Veterinary Medical Association Conference, ca. 1940s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00506)
  Description: Group of Southern Tier Veterinary Medical Association Conference attendees standing outside. Donald W. Baker is visible in the back row, farthest left.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6.5" x 4", 5" x 7", 2 prints on paper
- Donald W. Baker and five others, 1944 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00507)
  Description: Donald W. Baker and five others posed in a an outside group shot. Baker is fourth from the left.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4.5" x 7", 2 prints on paper
  Photographer (if other than Baker): Cornell Photo Science Service
- Donald W. Baker, George McConnell and four others, ca. 1940s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00508)
  Description: Donald W. Baker, George McConnell, both class of 1929, and four others posed in a group shot. Baker is third from the left. The man farthest left has a pipe in his mouth. McConnell is in between the two.
- Drs. Markham, Baker, Stone, Dansky, Schroeder, 1945 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00509)
  Description: "Group shot of Parisitology committee at Annual Conference, taken in the Dean's office in James Law Hall. Pictured in the back row, left to right are: Earl S. Markham, Donald W. Baker, and W.S. Stone. In the front row are Dansky, Schroeder and three unidentified men"
- Sir Frank Ware and D. W. Baker, 1947 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00510)
  Description: Candid of Sir Frank Ware and D. W. Baker standing outside in overcoats.
  Photographer (if other than Baker): Sol Goldberg for Cornell Photo Science Service
- Donald Baker and Don Leroh, 1945 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00511)
  Description: D. W. Baker and Don Leroh (Modern Farmer) talking at NBC radio station WEAF about cattle mange.
- S Public Health Service Epidemiology Course, 1960 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00512)
  Description: Epidemiology for Veterinarians at the Communicable Disease Center, US Public Health Service, Atlanta, Georgia, February 1-6, 1960. Donald W. Baker is pictured in the back row, third from right.
- Unidentified students with puppies, 1964 (Box 5c, Folder VPC.00513)
  Description: Unidentified students with puppies in a classroom. See also VPC.00496
- Donald W. Baker, ca. 1940s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00514)
  Description: Donald W. Baker with a cow in a barn
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9", 1 print on paper
  Photographer (if other than Baker): Unidentified
- Unidentified group, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00515)
  Description: Unidentified group. Could be a class reunion with faculty guests. Visible sitting in front row are (right to left): P.P. Levine, D.W. Baker, H.H. Dukes, Peter Olafson, M.E. Miller and A.G. Danks. One man in the unidentified crowd is holding a guitar.
- Unidentified group, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00516)
  Description: Unidentified group gathered around a dining table at a conference dinner. D.W. Baker is visible on the right.
- Donald W. Baker and unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00517)
  Description: Donald W. Baker and unidentified man at an Annual Conference. They are both wearing name tags and facing the camera. The unidentified man's initials appear to be "M. L."
- Souther Tier Veterinary Medical Association, 1945 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00518)
  Description: Posed group shot from a Southern Tier Veterinary Medical Association meeting. D. W Baker is visible in the center, back row. S.J. Roberts and D.H. Udall are kneeling in the front row, right. A.E. Merry is standing in the middle row, far right.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10" 4" x 6", 3 prints on paper
- Group Portrait of the Poultry School, 1945 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00519)
  Description: Group shot of the August 1945 Poultry School standing outside a Cornell building. S.J. Roberts is in the back row, far right. Earl S. Markham is in the back row, fourth from right. D.W. Baker is in the front row, seated third from right. F.S. Graziadei is
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10" 5" x 7", 2 prints on paper
- Donald W. Baker with a sheep, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00520)
  Description: Donald W. Baker with a sheep. He's wearing his hat
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 3 prints on cardboard
- Dr. Baker with students and a cat, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00521)
  Description: Dr. Baker with 3 unidentified students and a cat on a curb
- Donald W. Baker in the lab, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00522)
  Description: Donald W. Baker wearing lab coat in the lab near an unidentified black man is sitting in front of a microscope.
- D.W. Baker, unidentified black man, Meleney, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00523)
  Description: D. W. Baker, unidentified black man, and Dr. Meleney, Class of 1951
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 10", 1 print on cardboard
- D.W. Baker and students on Honor Day, 1959 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00524)
  Description: D. W. Baker, class of 1929, 2 unidentified students, and E. V. Mendel, class of 1959. Probably Honor Day, 1959. (see similar photo: VPC.00784)
- Dr. Donald W. Baker with students, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00525)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Donald W. Baker and students with buckets of intestines in a lab.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9", 4.5" x 8", 1 print on cardboard 3 prints on paper"
- Donald W. Baker and students, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00526)
  Description: Donald W. Baker and 5 students in a lab. They are examining something on a table.
- Donald W. Baker and 2 students with puppies, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00527)
  Description: Drs. Donald W. Baker and Lange (Class of 1955) and unidentified student with 2 puppies.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5", 3 prints on cardboard, 1 transparency"
- Dr. Donald W. Baker with students and pony, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00528)
  Description: Dr. Donald W. Baker and students with a pony during a parasitology lab demonstration.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4.5" x 7.5" [ 2 ], 7" x 9", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Dr. Donald W. Baker with students and pony, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00529)
- D.W. Baker and students in field with pony, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00530)
  Description: Donald W. Baker with students and pony (alternate view)
- D.W. Baker and students in field with pony, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00531)
- Donald W. Baker and students in the field with a pony, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00532)
  Description: Donald W. Baker in the field with students. Baker is facing the camera. The students are examining a pony, and there us a small dog in the foreground.
- Dr. Baker with students, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00533)
  Description: Dr. Baker with students and pony (back view)
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5", 5" x 7", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Dr. Baker and students, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00534)
  Description: Dr. Baker in a field with students. Baker one left of the farthest right, gesturing with one hand while the other is in his pocket.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5" x 7", " 2 prints on paper"
- Donald W. Baker, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00535)
  Description: Donald W. Baker examining soil with a stick. Two students are in the background.
- Donald W. Baker and students in the field, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00536)
  Description: Donald W. Baker in the field with students. He is crouched before a pile of dirt
- Donald W. Baker and students in the field, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00537)
  Description: Donald W. Baker in the field with students. Baker is examining something in his hands while the students look on.
- Donald W. Baker and students in the field, ca. 1960s (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00538)
  Description: Donald W. Baker in the field with students and cows. Baker is in the middle behind a tilted wooden something. Roof of a barn is visible in background. Everyone else's backs are turned to the camera.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9" 5" x 7", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Donald W. Baker with cows and students, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00539)
- Donald W. Baker and students, 1964 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00540)
  Description: Donald W. Baker posing with 18 students from his History of Veterinary Medicine Class. Visible are Stan Rothwell, Richard P. Henry, Robert Mueller, Allan W. Prowter, Harold P. Gill, David K. Hagan, Lynn Jones, Phillip Schurman, Kenneth D. Feldman, Gary Si
  Size and Number of Photographs: "5"" x 8"" 7"" x 10"10" x 13"", "4 prints on paper 3 prints on cardboard"
- D. W. Baker and Students, ca. 1963 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00541)
  Description: D. W. Baker and students examining a sheep. At least some are members of the class of 1963.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "8.5"" x 11"" 8" x 10", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- Nutrition Conference, 1965 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00542)
  Description: "Group shot outside Shurman Hall of a Nutrition Conference, New York State Veterinary Medical Society, January 5, 1965. D. W. Baker is at far left. A. G. Danks is third from right, front row, in light coat and cane. Clayton E. De Camp is far right holding"
- New York State Veterinary Medical Society group, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00543)
  Description: New York State Veterinary Medical Society group. In the back row are, left to right, 2 unidentified men, John Murray and Henry Grossman. Seated are Charles Fletcher, D. W. Baker, Howard K. "Cap" Fuller, and Clayton E. De Camp.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5", 1 print on particle board
- 5 Presidents of New York State Veterinary Medical Society, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00544)
  Description: 5 presidents of the New York State Veterinary Medical Society. Pictured left to right are: D. W. Baker, H. C. Stephenson, Peter Olafson, A. G. Danks and M. G. Fincher
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 7", 3 prints on cardboard
- Group at dinner meeting, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00545)
  Description: Group standing and chatting at a dinner meeting. Pictured, left to right, are: Donald Bixby, class of 1935; Richard Fortune, class of 1935; unidentified man; Wilson Bell, class of 1939; M.G. Fincher (with back turned); Edwin Foster, class of 1935; unid
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9", 3 prints on cardboard
- D.W. Baker and Louis Juliand, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00546)
  Description: D.W. Baker and Louis Juliand, Class of 1900.
- Dr. and Mrs. Helms and unidentified couple, ca. 1950s (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00547)
  Description: Dr. Orland E. Helms (Class of 1920), Mrs. Helms and unidentified couple. The four are posed outside. The two women are in the center. The unidentified couple is on the left. Caption on the back of one print says " Margaret H. Hayden, class of 1966 and he
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 7.5" 7"" x 9.5"" 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 2 prints on paper"
- 2 unidentified men, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00548)
  Description: 2 unidentified men at a conference. One on the left has glasses and is facing right. The one on the right has no glasses and is facing the camera but looking to the right. Both are wearing suits and name tags.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "9.5"" x 9.5"" 10"" x 11"" 10"" x 10"" 5"" x 9""", 3 prints on cardboard (2 cropped) 1 print on paper
- Bircher and Graziadei, ca. 1950 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00549)
  Description: Candid of Irwin George Bircher, class of 1929 and Frank S. Graziadei, class of 1929. They are seated, wearing Annual Conference badges.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 9", 1 print on cardboard
- Irwin George Bircher and Frank S. Graziadei, ca. 1960s (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00550)
  Description: Candid of Irwin George Bircher, class of 1929 and Frank S. Graziadei, class of 1929. They are both laughing. Bircher is wearing a hat.
- George McConnell and Frank S. Graziadei, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00551)
  Description: George McConnell and F. S. Graziadei, Both Class of 1929, climbing a fence with sheep in a pen
- Sam Johnson and George McConnell, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00552)
  Description: Sam Johnson and George E. McConnell, both class of 1929, shaking hands at an Annual Conference
- Harry Temple and Seth Johnson at the Dedication of Research Tower, 1963 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00553)
  Description: Harry Temple and Seth Johnson (both Class of 1929) at the Dedication of Research Tower, standing in front of James Law Auditorium. Also visible is Lincoln Field, class of 1930.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "1.5"" x 7"" 2 6"" x 9"" 4"" x 8""", 1 print on paper 3 prints on cardboard"
- Seth Johnson and Johanna Asmus Sutorius, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00554)
  Description: Seth Johnson and Johanna Asmus Sutorius, (both Class of 1929). She is wearing a fur coat and has her back to the camera. Someone holding flowers is standing just off camera.
- Seth Johnson, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00555)
  Description: Seth Johnson, class of 1929, standing with a cigar in his hand and his mouth open.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5" 5" x 7", 2 prints on cardboard
- Sam Johnson and two unidentified men, 1961 (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00556)
  Description: Samuel A. Johnson, Class of 1929, and two unidentified men in a barn. Sam is in the middle looking at the camera, with his arms crossed. The other two men are looking at each other
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5" x 7" (cropped) 3" x 5", 4 prints on paper
- Sam Johnson and unidentified man, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00557)
  Description: Samuel A. Johnson, Class of 1929, and unidentified man standing at the corner of State Street and Green Street in Ithaca
- Joseph R. Kaul and Charles A. Kehr?, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00558)
  Description: Two men standing at the corner of State Street and Green Street in Ithaca. Names written on the back read Joseph R. Kaul, Class of 1942, and Charles A. Kehr, Class of 1932, but there are no such graduates of Cornell for those dates. "Ulmer '28" is also w
- Clifford Henry Hoppenstedt, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00559)
  Description: Clifford Henry Hoppenstedt, Class of 1935, standing at the corner of State Street and Green Street in Ithaca
- Dr. and Mrs. Joseph Thomas, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00560)
  Description: Dr. and Mrs. Joseph A. Thomas, class of 1929. There are shelves of pharmaceuticals in the background. They're both wearing plaid
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 12", 1 print on cardboard
- Jane Benson, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00561)
  Description: Candid of Jane Whallon Benson, class of 1947, and unidentified man. She is holding a corsage.
- Selma Levine, 1961 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00562)
  Description: Candid of Selma Levine, wife of P. P. Levine. She is wearing a badge with a flag on it.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 7" 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Philip Levine, Selma Levine, and Dorsey Bruner at a buffet table, 1961 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00563)
  Description: Philip Levine, Selma Levine, and Dorsey Bruner at a buffet table
- P. P. Levin ,Selma Levine and Clara Gage, 1961 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00564)
  Description: Clara Gage pinning a name tag on P. P. Levine, class of 1931. Selma Levine is also pictured
- Charles Morris?, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00565)
  Description: Candid of a man identified as Charles Morris, class of 1917, seated and looking at the camera, pen and paper in hand. But VPC.00566is a similar looking man, with the same tie, whose name tag doesn't look like it reads "Morris."
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 8.5", 9" x 9", 10" x 10", 3 prints on cardboard
- Charles Morris?, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00566)
  Description: Candid of a man who looks like the man identified as Charles Morris in VPC.00567.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard
- Drs. Brown, Moore, Stone, Snook, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00567)
  Description: "Four Annual Conference attendees seated in a lounge. From Left to right: Albert Brown, Class of 1915; Erwin V. Moore, Class of 1917; W.S. Stone, class of 1935; and George Snook, Class of 1938."
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6" x 8.5", 2 prints on cardboard
- 4 unidentified men, 1965 (Box 3 and 5c, Folder VPC.00568)
  Description: Four unidentified men. Man facing the camera has glasses and a freckle or a mole above his lip. Man with back turned could be Lincoln Field. Could be an Annual Conference dinner.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5", 2 prints on cardboard (cropped), 1 print on paper
- Unidentified man and woman, 1965 (Box 3, Folder VPC.00569)
  Description: Unidentified man and woman talking to another man at a dinner party. Could be an Annual Conference dinner.
- Groups talking at a dinner, 1965 (Box 5c, Folder VPC.00570)
  Description: Groups talking at a dinner. Could be an Annual Conference dinner. Peter Olafson is visible in the background
- Groups talking at a dinner, 1965 (Box 5c, Folder VPC.00571)
  Description: Groups talking at a dinner. Could be an Annual Conference dinner. Peter Olafson talking to a couple in the foreground
- Groups talking at a dinner, 1965 (Box 5c, Folder VPC.00572)
  Description: Groups talking at a dinner. Could be an Annual Conference dinner. Two women with backs turned in the foreground.
- Bill Kaplan, ca. 1960s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00574)
  Description: Bill Kaplan, Class of 1946, sitting in a chair. His argyle socks are showing
- Harold MacMurray and Frank McClelland, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00575)
  Description: Harold MacMurray and Frank McClelland examining a chicken (?), one is smoking a pipe.
- Harold MacMurray and Frank McClelland, ca. 1950s (Box 3, Folder VPC.00576)
  Description: Harold MacMurray and Frank McClelland examining several trays of fowl carcasses. One is smoking a pipe.
- Dr. Benson and 2 unidentified men (Box 3, Folder VPC.00577)